<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>prosody on </title>
    <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/tags/prosody/</link>
    <description>Recent content in prosody on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mcanzi.github.io/tags/prosody/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Intonational alignment in second language acquisition {M Canzi, C Ulbrich}</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/intonational-alignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/intonational-alignment/</guid>
      <description>Output  (2023) Ulbrich, C., &amp;amp; Canzi, M. Intonational alignment in second language acquisition. Speech Communication 146, 70-81  Abstract This study examines how proficient second language speakers of Belfast English and Northern Standard German realize cross-linguistic differences in intonational phonological categories and their gradient phonetic implementation. Belfast English and Northern Standard German select two different intonation patterns for nuclear pitch accents in declarative utterances. Northern Standard German features a falling pitch accent pattern.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prosody of Case Markers in Urdu {B Mumtaz, M Canzi, M Butt}</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/urdu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/urdu/</guid>
      <description>Output  (2021) Mumtaz, B., Canzi, M., &amp;amp; Butt, M. Prosody of Case Markers in Urdu. Proc. Interspeech 2021  Abstract This paper studies the prosody of case clitics in Urdu, for which various different claims exist in the literature. We conducted a production experiment and controlled for effects potentially arising from the phonetics of the case clitics, the syntactic function they express and clausal position. We find that case clitics are incorporated into the prosodic phrase of the noun and that they become part of the overall LH contour found on accentual phrases in Urdu/Hindi.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
