<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>phonetics on </title>
    <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/tags/phonetics/</link>
    <description>Recent content in phonetics on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mcanzi.github.io/tags/phonetics/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Effects of a face mask on the perception of English fricatives by native speakers of Greek {A Tsaroucha, T Rathcke, M Canzi}</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/icgl15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/icgl15/</guid>
      <description>Output   (2023) A. Tsaroucha, T. Rathcke, &amp;amp; Canzi, M.. Effects of a face mask on the perception of English fricatives by native speakers of Greek. Proc. ICGL15
  (2022) *Tsaroucha, A., Rathcke, T., &amp;amp; Canzi, M. Effects of a face mask on the perception of English fricatives by native speakers of Greek. Talk presented at the 15th International Conference on Greek Linguistics (ICGL15).
  (2021) *Rathcke, T.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prosody of Case Markers in Urdu {B Mumtaz, M Canzi, M Butt}</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/urdu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/urdu/</guid>
      <description>Output  (2021) Mumtaz, B., Canzi, M., &amp;amp; Butt, M. Prosody of Case Markers in Urdu. Proc. Interspeech 2021  Abstract This paper studies the prosody of case clitics in Urdu, for which various different claims exist in the literature. We conducted a production experiment and controlled for effects potentially arising from the phonetics of the case clitics, the syntactic function they express and clausal position. We find that case clitics are incorporated into the prosodic phrase of the noun and that they become part of the overall LH contour found on accentual phrases in Urdu/Hindi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The effect of lexical frequency on vowel phonation as a correlate of /t/-glottaling {S Coretta, M Canzi}</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/glottaling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/glottaling/</guid>
      <description>Output  (2018) Coretta, S. &amp;amp; Canzi, M. The effect of lexical frequency on vowel phonation as a correlate of /t/-glottaling. Talk presented at the Linguistic Association of Great Britain (LAGB) conference at the University of Sheffield.  Abstract Introduction. Lexical frequency is known to modulate the effects of a phonetic bias on speech production, such that high-frequency words show a stronger effect for a particular bias since they are exposed more often to that bias (Bybee 2004).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inter- and intra- speaker variation of F(0, 1, 2) &amp; vowel duration in soft, neutral and loud speech in Italian {M Canzi}</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/forensic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/forensic/</guid>
      <description>Output   (2018) Canzi, M. The Forensic implications of comparing soft, neutral and loud speech. Talk presented at the Manchester Forum in Linguistics (mFiL) at	The University of Manchester
  (2018) Canzi, M A quantitative analysis of inter- and intra- speaker variation of F0, F1, F2 and vowel duration in soft, neutral and loud speech in Italian. Poster presented at the British Association of Academics in Phonetics (BAAP) at the University of Kent.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
