<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>production on </title>
    <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/tags/production/</link>
    <description>Recent content in production on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mcanzi.github.io/tags/production/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[Ulbrich, C. &amp; Canzi, M.] Intonational alignment in second language acquisition</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/intonational-alignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/intonational-alignment/</guid>
      <description>Publications  (Submitted) Ulbrich, C., &amp;amp; Canzi, M. Intonational alignment in second language acquisition. Speech Communication  Abstract This study examines how proficient second language speakers of Belfast English and Northern Standard German realize cross-linguistic differences in intonational phonological categories and their gradient phonetic implementation. Belfast English and Northern Standard German select two different intonation patterns for nuclear pitch accents in declarative utterances. Northern Standard German features a falling pitch accent pattern.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Coretta, S. &amp; Canzi, M.] The effect of lexical frequency on vowel phonation as a correlate of /t/-glottaling</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/glottaling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/glottaling/</guid>
      <description>Presentations Coretta, S. &amp;amp; Canzi, M. The effect of lexical frequency on vowel phonation as a correlate of /t/-	glottaling. Talk presented at the Linguistic Association of Great Britain (LAGB) conference at the University of Sheffield.
Abstract Introduction. Lexical frequency is known to modulate the effects of a phonetic bias on speech production, such that high-frequency words show a stronger effect for a particular bias since they are exposed more often to that bias (Bybee 2004).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Canzi, M.] Inter- and intra- speaker variation of F(0, 1, 2) &amp; vowel duration in soft, neutral and loud speech in Italian.</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/forensic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/forensic/</guid>
      <description>Conferences Canzi, M. (2018) The Forensic implications of comparing soft, neutral and loud speech. Talk presented at the Manchester Forum in Linguistics (mFiL) at	The University of Manchester
Canzi, M (2018) A quantitative analysis of inter- and intra- speaker variation of F0, F1, F2 and vowel duration in soft, neutral and loud speech in Italian. Poster presented at the British Association of Academics in Phonetics (BAAP) at the University of Kent.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
