<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mcanzi.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>curriculum vitae</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/skills/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/skills/education/</guid>
      <description>Summary: Formally trained in quantitative research in phonetics and speech sciences. Since 2021, I am a data scientist and laboratory manager in the linguistics department at Universität Konstanz, where I teach MA-level courses in &amp;ldquo;Statistics&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Advanced Statistics&amp;rdquo;, &amp;ldquo;Forensic Speech Science&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;Eye Tracking &amp;amp; Pupillometry&amp;rdquo; for linguistics students. I am an avid R coder. I also advocate for sensible experimental designs, clear and reproducible data science and honest scientific communication.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>film photography</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/photos/japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/photos/japan/</guid>
      <description>Japan, September – October 2024: Traveling south from Nikko to Kagoshima, stopping through Tokyo, Osaka, Nara, and Kyushu (Fukuoka, Nagasaki, Beppu, Kagoshima). Shooting on a Leica M6 with a 35mm pre-aspherical lens and Kodak 50D (rated +1) to capture the mix of city life, nature, and everyday moments along the way.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>research</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/research/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/research/</guid>
      <description>Synchronised movement and individual rhythmic skill influence the perception of temporal structure in spoken language Tamara Rathcke, Eline Smit, Rachel Yue &amp;amp; Massimiliano Canzi (2024)
Attention, Perception &amp;amp; Psychophysics, 1-17 | doi: 10.3758/s13414-024-02893-8
The subjective experience of time flow in speech deviates from the sound acoustics in substantial ways. The present study focuses on the perceptual tendency to regularize time intervals found in speech but not in other types of sounds with a similar temporal structure.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>workshops</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/teaching/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/teaching/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Hello!
I&amp;rsquo;m now offering a wide range of workshops both online and in-person, tailored specifically to your learning needs. With my background as a data scientist in a linguistics department, I&amp;rsquo;ve had the chance to collaborate with dozens of research projects, and support over 50 students in achieving their research goals, in addition to teaching hundreds more.
My workshops delve into the fascinating world of quantitative methods, from introductory short courses on linear regression and linear mixed effect models to the more intricate generalized additive mixed models (GAMMs).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
