<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title></title>
    <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mcanzi.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unmasking the truf: impact of community masks on the perception of voiceless fricatives in English {M Canzi, T Rathcke}</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/icphs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/icphs/</guid>
      <description>Output (2023) Canzi, M., &amp;amp; Rathcke, T. Unmasking the truf: impact of community masks on the perception of English fricatives. Proc. ICPhS 2023
(2023) *Canzi, M, &amp;amp; Rathcke, T.. Unmasking the truf: Impact of community masks on the perception of voiceless fricatives in English. Talk presented at ICPhS 2023
(2021) *Rathcke, T., &amp;amp; *Canzi, M. Deaf by face mask? Impact of community masks on the perception of voiceless fricatives in English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Intonational alignment in second language acquisition {M Canzi, C Ulbrich}</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/intonational-alignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/intonational-alignment/</guid>
      <description>Output (2023) Ulbrich, C., &amp;amp; Canzi, M. Intonational alignment in second language acquisition. Speech Communication 146, 70-81 Abstract This study examines how proficient second language speakers of Belfast English and Northern Standard German realize cross-linguistic differences in intonational phonological categories and their gradient phonetic implementation. Belfast English and Northern Standard German select two different intonation patterns for nuclear pitch accents in declarative utterances. Northern Standard German features a falling pitch accent pattern.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effects of a face mask on the perception of English fricatives by native speakers of Greek {A Tsaroucha, T Rathcke, M Canzi}</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/icgl15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/icgl15/</guid>
      <description>Output (2023) A. Tsaroucha, T. Rathcke, &amp;amp; Canzi, M.. Effects of a face mask on the perception of English fricatives by native speakers of Greek. Proc. ICGL15
(2022) *Tsaroucha, A., Rathcke, T., &amp;amp; Canzi, M. Effects of a face mask on the perception of English fricatives by native speakers of Greek. Talk presented at the 15th International Conference on Greek Linguistics (ICGL15).
(2021) *Rathcke, T., &amp;amp; *Canzi, M. Deaf by face mask?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Prosody of Case Markers in Urdu {B Mumtaz, M Canzi, M Butt}</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/urdu/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/urdu/</guid>
      <description>Output (2021) Mumtaz, B., Canzi, M., &amp;amp; Butt, M. Prosody of Case Markers in Urdu. Proc. Interspeech 2021 Abstract This paper studies the prosody of case clitics in Urdu, for which various different claims exist in the literature. We conducted a production experiment and controlled for effects potentially arising from the phonetics of the case clitics, the syntactic function they express and clausal position. We find that case clitics are incorporated into the prosodic phrase of the noun and that they become part of the overall LH contour found on accentual phrases in Urdu/Hindi.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What PMN? Investigating phonological processing in semantics-free speech perception with ERP {M Canzi, W Kimper}</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/erp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/erp/</guid>
      <description>Presentations Canzi, M., &amp;amp; Kimper, W. (2020). Processing speech sounds in speech(-like) perception: an ERP study. Posters accepted at the British Association of Academics in Phonetics at the University of York / PhonolEEGy at Université Côte d&amp;rsquo;Azur.
Canzi, M. (2019). Don&amp;rsquo;t let me be misunderstood: Exploring early phonological and lexical processing in speech perception. Talk presented at the Manchester Forum in Linguistics (mFiL) at The University of Manchester
Canzi, M. (2019).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The effect of lexical frequency on vowel phonation as a correlate of /t/-glottaling {S Coretta, M Canzi}</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/glottaling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/glottaling/</guid>
      <description>Output (2018) Coretta, S. &amp;amp; Canzi, M. The effect of lexical frequency on vowel phonation as a correlate of /t/-glottaling. Talk presented at the Linguistic Association of Great Britain (LAGB) conference at the University of Sheffield. Abstract Introduction. Lexical frequency is known to modulate the effects of a phonetic bias on speech production, such that high-frequency words show a stronger effect for a particular bias since they are exposed more often to that bias (Bybee 2004).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Inter- and intra- speaker variation of F(0, 1, 2) &amp; vowel duration in soft, neutral and loud speech in Italian {M Canzi}</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/forensic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/forensic/</guid>
      <description>Output (2018) Canzi, M. The Forensic implications of comparing soft, neutral and loud speech. Talk presented at the Manchester Forum in Linguistics (mFiL) at	The University of Manchester
(2018) Canzi, M A quantitative analysis of inter- and intra- speaker variation of F0, F1, F2 and vowel duration in soft, neutral and loud speech in Italian. Poster presented at the British Association of Academics in Phonetics (BAAP) at the University of Kent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/photos/japan/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/photos/japan/</guid>
      <description>Between 26.09.23 and 17.10.23, I journeyed through Japan, capturing its architecture and street life. All images were taken with the Sony A7IV mirrorless camera, paired with a 14 mm GM lens.
Tokyo I (29.09.23)
Tokyo II (01.10.23)
Tokyo III (01.10.23)
Hakone (04.10.23)
Hakone II (04.10.23)
Hakone III (04.10.23)
Nikko I (05.10.23)
Nikko II (06.10.23)
Nikko III (06.10.23)
Nikko IV (06.10.23)
Nikko IV (07.10.23)
Takayama I (08.10.23)
Takayama II (09.10.23)
Takayama III (09.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curriculum Vitae</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/skills/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 02 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/skills/education/</guid>
      <description>Employment (1/2021-//////) Akademischer Mitarbeiter (100% TVL-13) at Universität Konstanz: Tenured lecturer in Statistics, Advanced Statistics, and Introduction to Forensic Speech Science for MA-level students. Data curation, analysis and visualisation in R. Supervision of MA and BA students. Staff training in behavioral and physiological research methods.
(2/2018-9/2019) Psycholinguistics Laboratory Manager at The University of Manchester
(2/2018-2/2020) Graduate Teaching Assistant at The University of Manchester
Forensic Linguistics (Dr Andrea Nini) Handling Data (Dr Patrycja Strycharczuk) Language, Mind &amp;amp; Brain (Dr Wendell Kimper) Psycholinguistics (Dr Thea-Cameron Faulkner) Sounds of Language (Dr Patrycja Strycharczuk) Education (2017-2021) PhD in Linguistics at The University of Manchester.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>workshops</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/teaching/teaching/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/teaching/teaching/</guid>
      <description>Hello!
I&amp;rsquo;m now offering a wide range of workshops both online and in-person, tailored specifically to your learning needs. With my background as a data scientist in a linguistics department, I&amp;rsquo;ve had the chance to collaborate with dozens of research projects, and support over 50 students in achieving their research goals, in addition to teaching hundreds more.
My workshops delve into the fascinating world of quantitative methods, from introductory short courses on linear regression and linear mixed effect models to the more intricate generalized additive mixed models (GAMMs).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
