<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Massimiliano Canzi</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Massimiliano Canzi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>information flow order in speech perception</title>
      <link>/project/erp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/erp/</guid>
      <description>Overview Aims and Objectives
• To explore how different levels of speech processing interact with each other to facilitate the understanding of speech.
• To test experimentally the relative timing of different levels in speech processing.
• To collect EEG (electroencephalography) data from a relevant sample size on brain re- sponses to auditory stimuli.
Background: Two main currents of thought in psycholinguistics have categorised speech per- ception to be either unidirectional or interactive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Goldfish (LP) by Asami Yamazaki</title>
      <link>/music/asami/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/asami/</guid>
      <description>Overview tags: lo-fi, ambient, post-rock, noise
The first LP by the solo project Asami Yamazaki (Massimiliano Canzi) features tracks written between 2013 and 2015. The entire LP was written, played, recorded, mixed and mastered by Massimiliano Canzi with the exception of these tracks:
Okinawa:
Massimiliano Canzi: beats, synths, samples, recording, mixing, mastering. Marco Bergamaschi: samples, recording, mixing, mastering.
Superstereo:
Massimiliano Canzi: writing, beats, synths, bass, mixing, mastering. Mario Blaconà: guitars</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the effect of lexical frequency on vowel phonation as a correlate of t glottaling</title>
      <link>/project/glottaling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/glottaling/</guid>
      <description>Presentations 2018 Stefano Coretta, Massimiliano Canzi The effect of lexical frequency on vowel phonation as a correlate of /t/- glottaling. Talk presented at the Linguistic Association of Great Britain (LAGB) conference in Sheffield, UK. 11-14th September, 2018.
Resources You can find the research compendium (including data, analysis, code and slides/poster) for this project at the following link:
LAGB 2018
Abstract Introduction. Lexical frequency is known to modulate the effects of a phonetic bias on speech production, such that high-frequency words show a stronger effect for a particular bias since they are exposed more often to that bias (Bybee 2004).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continental (EP) by Fukushima Sushi</title>
      <link>/music/fukushima/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Sep 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/fukushima/</guid>
      <description> Overview tags: post rock, instrumental rock, stoner, lo-fi, electronic
Massimiliano Canzi: guitar, vocals (in &amp;lsquo;Nothing&amp;rsquo;) and production
Mario Blaconà: guitar, vocals
Giorgio Mussi: bass
Jacopo Invernizzi: drums
Tracklist  Concrete
 DUI
 Post-colonian rock
 Nothing
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the forensic implications of comparing soft, neutral and loud speech</title>
      <link>/project/forensic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/project/forensic/</guid>
      <description>Presentations 2018 Massimiliano Canzi The Forensic implications of comparing soft, neutral and loud speech. Talk presented at the Manchester Forum in Linguistics (mFiL) in Manchester, UK. 26-27th April, 2018.
2018 Massimiliano Canzi A quantitative analysis of inter- and intra- speaker variation of F0, F1, F2 and vowel duration in soft, neutral and loud speech in Italian. Poster presented at the Colloquium of the British Association of Academic Phoneticians (BAAP) in Canterbury, UK.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Clouds in a Bundle (EP) by mymindasacircuit</title>
      <link>/music/mmaac/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/music/mmaac/</guid>
      <description> Overview tags: chillout, ambient, instrumental, loops
Massimiliano Canzi: guitars, bass, production, keyboard
Roland Erulo: guitars, production, keyboard, drums
Tracklist  Intro
 Rain
 Afternoon
 Choices
 Immersion
 Soundtrack of a movie never made
 Absent Sun
  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Atom: useful packages</title>
      <link>/posts/atom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/atom/</guid>
      <description>Atom is a powerful open-source text editor with embedded Git control. Atom is unique because of its 7000+ plugins (packages) which are usually license-free and community-built. Atom supports syntax highlighting natively for more than 30 programming languages. The number is esponentially increased when external packages are installed.
If you have Atom installed, you can search packages simply by opening up a new terminal window and typing apm search keyword</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>new psycholinguistics lab website</title>
      <link>/posts/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/education/</guid>
      <description>Finally, Manchester&amp;rsquo;s psycholinguistics laboratory gets a revamped website. Use it to check the lab&amp;rsquo;s schedule and to book the lab for yourself. Alternatively, you can always e-mail me directly for any queries or booking of the lab.
You can find the lab&amp;rsquo;s website &amp;gt;&amp;gt;&amp;gt; here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>education</title>
      <link>/2018/09/17/education/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/09/17/education/</guid>
      <description>University (2017 - Present) PhD in Linguistics. The University of Manchester. Information flow order in speech perception: An electro-physiological approach to the architecture of perception and grammar. Supervised by: Dr Wendell Kimper, Dr Patrycja Strycharczuk.
(2016 - 2017) MSc in Forensic Speech Science. University of York. Dissertation: Do expectations elicited by a speaker’s somatic features mediate the perception of the speaker’s voice?. Supervised by: Dr Dom Watt.
(2015 - 2016) MA in Linguistics.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>teaching and work experience</title>
      <link>/2018/09/17/teaching-and-work-experience/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/09/17/teaching-and-work-experience/</guid>
      <description>Teaching experience (January 2018 - May 2018): Teaching Assistant in Forensic Linguistics. The University of Manchester. Course code: LELA3162. Course convenor: Dr Andrea Nini.
(September 2018 - January 2019): Teaching Assistant in Psycholinguistics. The University of Manchester. Course convenor: Dr Thea Cameron-Faulkner.
Work experience (April 2018 - Present): Research Assistant. Research assistant for the Northern Englishes Project. The University of Manchester.
(January 2018 - Present): Psycholinguistics Laboratory Assistant. The University of Manchester.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>awards</title>
      <link>/2018/09/14/awards/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2018/09/14/awards/</guid>
      <description>Awards 2018 Stefano Coretta, Massimiliano Canzi (joint winners) of
Best Student Abstract submitted to the LAGB (Linguistic Association of Great Britain) 2018 conference with the abstract titled: ‘The effect of lexical frequency on vowel phonation as a correlate of /t/- glottaling’</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>academic skills</title>
      <link>/2017/09/22/academic-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/22/academic-skills/</guid>
      <description>Speech Analysis: Praat (sample script below), Wavesurfer
Speech Manipulation: Praat, iZotope, Audacity
ERP/EEG: Matlab, ERPlab/EEGlab
Experimental Design: E-Prime, PsychoPy, Presentation (Neurobehavioral Systems)
Statistical Analysis &amp;amp; Data Visualisation: RStudio, R markdown (sample script below)
Other programming languages known: Python
Text typesetting: TeX, Microsoft Word
Data visualisation Hi, here&amp;rsquo;s some random plots I made in ggplot!
F1-F2 vowel plots for male Italian speakers in neutral and loud speech.
Sample of R script The following sample of an R project is meant to read data, clean it, run mixed effect models and create visual representation of results with ggplot.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>