<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Praat on Massimiliano Canzi</title>
    <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/tags/praat/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Praat on Massimiliano Canzi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mcanzi.github.io/tags/praat/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Atom: useful packages</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/posts/i/atom/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/posts/i/atom/</guid>
      <description>Atom is a powerful open-source text editor with embedded Git control. Atom is unique because of its 7000+ plugins (packages) which are usually license-free and community-built. Atom supports syntax highlighting natively for more than 30 programming languages. The number is esponentially increased when external packages are installed.
If you have Atom installed, you can search packages simply by opening up a new terminal window and typing apm search keyword
massimiliano@Massimilianos-MacBook-Pro ~&amp;gt; apm search language-r Search Results For &#39;language-r&#39; (29) ├── language-r A language description and snippets for R (67671 downloads, 83 stars) ├── atom-language-r A language description and snippets for R (2487 downloads, 8 stars) ├── language-cup A short description of your language package (621 downloads, 0 stars) ├── language-hcl Syntax support for the HashiCorp Configuration Language (9578 downloads, 25 stars) ├── language-jcm JaCaMo Project Language (114 downloads, 0 stars) ├── language-v0 Language package for Imparato internal v0 source files.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>academic skills</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/skills/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/skills/skills/</guid>
      <description>Speech Analysis:	Praat, Wavesurfer
Speech Manipulation:	Praat, iZotope, Audacity
ERP/EEG:	Matlab, ERPlab/EEGlab, ActiView, Biosemi EEG systems
Experimental Design:	Presentation (Neurobehavioral Systems), PsychoPy, E-Prime
Statistical Analysis &amp;amp; Data Visualisation:	R (w/ tidyverse), Python
Image and video manipulation Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Lightroom, Adobe Premiere Pro
Languages Italian (Native), English (C2), Portuguese (B2), German (A1)
Other programming languages known:	Python
Text typesetting:	TeX, Microsoft Word</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
