<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>erp on Massimiliano Canzi</title>
    <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/tags/erp/</link>
    <description>Recent content in erp on Massimiliano Canzi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mcanzi.github.io/tags/erp/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Don&#39;t let me be misunderstood. Exploring early speech perception</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/erp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/erp/</guid>
      <description>The aim of our study is to determine whether phonological information is pro- cessed earlier than semantic information in a feed-forward fashion during perception (McQueen et al. 2009) or whether di􏰁erent levels of speech (e.g. phonological, semantic) can mediate one another during perception and processing (McClelland &amp;amp; Elman 1986). In order to achieve this, we plan to investigate the nature of early event-related potentials (ERP), shifts in electrical poten- tial in the brain as a response to a particular event, to determine whether phonological and lexical features of speech are processed by the brain at di􏰁erent times.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>academic skills</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/2017/09/22/academic-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/2017/09/22/academic-skills/</guid>
      <description>Speech Analysis: Praat (sample script below), Wavesurfer
Speech Manipulation: Praat, iZotope, Audacity
ERP/EEG: Matlab, ERPlab/EEGlab
Experimental Design: E-Prime, PsychoPy, Presentation (Neurobehavioral Systems)
Statistical Analysis &amp;amp; Data Visualisation: RStudio, R markdown (sample script below)
Other programming languages known: Python
Text typesetting: TeX, Microsoft Word
Data visualisation Hi, here&amp;rsquo;s some random plots I made in ggplot!
F1-F2 vowel plots for male Italian speakers in neutral and loud speech.
Sample of R script The following sample of an R project is meant to read data, clean it, run mixed effect models and create visual representation of results with ggplot.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>