<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>perception on </title>
    <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/tags/perception/</link>
    <description>Recent content in perception on </description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mcanzi.github.io/tags/perception/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Unmasking the truf: impact of community masks on the perception of voiceless fricatives in English {M Canzi, T Rathcke}</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/icphs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/icphs/</guid>
      <description>Output (2023) Canzi, M., &amp;amp; Rathcke, T. Unmasking the truf: impact of community masks on the perception of English fricatives. Proc. ICPhS 2023
(2023) *Canzi, M, &amp;amp; Rathcke, T.. Unmasking the truf: Impact of community masks on the perception of voiceless fricatives in English. Talk presented at ICPhS 2023
(2021) *Rathcke, T., &amp;amp; *Canzi, M. Deaf by face mask? Impact of community masks on the perception of voiceless fricatives in English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Effects of a face mask on the perception of English fricatives by native speakers of Greek {A Tsaroucha, T Rathcke, M Canzi}</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/icgl15/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/icgl15/</guid>
      <description>Output (2023) A. Tsaroucha, T. Rathcke, &amp;amp; Canzi, M.. Effects of a face mask on the perception of English fricatives by native speakers of Greek. Proc. ICGL15
(2022) *Tsaroucha, A., Rathcke, T., &amp;amp; Canzi, M. Effects of a face mask on the perception of English fricatives by native speakers of Greek. Talk presented at the 15th International Conference on Greek Linguistics (ICGL15).
(2021) *Rathcke, T., &amp;amp; *Canzi, M. Deaf by face mask?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>What PMN? Investigating phonological processing in semantics-free speech perception with ERP {M Canzi, W Kimper}</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/erp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/erp/</guid>
      <description>Presentations Canzi, M., &amp;amp; Kimper, W. (2020). Processing speech sounds in speech(-like) perception: an ERP study. Posters accepted at the British Association of Academics in Phonetics at the University of York / PhonolEEGy at Université Côte d&amp;rsquo;Azur.
Canzi, M. (2019). Don&amp;rsquo;t let me be misunderstood: Exploring early phonological and lexical processing in speech perception. Talk presented at the Manchester Forum in Linguistics (mFiL) at The University of Manchester
Canzi, M. (2019).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
