<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Massimiliano Canzi</title>
    <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Massimiliano Canzi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mcanzi.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>[Ulbrich, C. &amp; Canzi, M.] Intonational alignment in second language acquisition</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/intonational-alignment/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 19 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/intonational-alignment/</guid>
      <description>Publications &amp;hellip;
Abstract This study examines how proficient second language speakers of Belfast English and Northern Standard German realize cross-linguistic differences in intonational phonological categories and their gradient phonetic implementation. Belfast English and Northern Standard German select two different intonation patterns for nuclear pitch accents in declarative utterances. Northern Standard German features a falling pitch accent pattern. In Belfast English, a rising intonation contour is realised.
The experiment compared the production of phonologically different pitch accents in declarative utterances and gradient acoustic characteristics of pitch range in utterancefinal position and peak alignment in nuclear pitch accents produced by native Belfast English learners of Northern Standard German with that of native Northern Standard German learners of Belfast English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Tsaroucha, A., Rathcke. T. &amp; Canzi. M.] Effects of a face mask on the perception of English fricatives by native speakers of Greek</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/icgl15/gre-models/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 31 Mar 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/icgl15/gre-models/</guid>
      <description>Presentations …
 Abstract Background. The ongoing COVID-19 pandemic has made a daily use of face masks mandatory. This has greatly influenced the everyday communication since face masks interfere with both acoustic and visual cues that would otherwise be available to interlocutors in spoken interaction. The present study focuses on the effect of this interference for the perception of 4 voiceless English fricatives: dental /θ/, labiodental /f/, alveolar /s/, and postalveolar /ʃ/.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Canzi, M. &amp; Kimper, W.] What PMN? Investigating phonological processing in semantics-free speech perception with ERP</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/erp/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Apr 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/erp/</guid>
      <description>Presentations Canzi, M., &amp;amp; Kimper, W. (2020). Processing speech sounds in speech(-like) perception: an ERP study. Posters accepted at the British Association of Academics in Phonetics at the University of York / PhonolEEGy at Université Côte d&amp;rsquo;Azur.
Canzi, M. (2019). Don&amp;rsquo;t let me be misunderstood: Exploring early phonological and lexical processing in speech perception. Talk presented at the Manchester Forum in Linguistics (mFiL) at The University of Manchester
Canzi, M. (2019).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Coretta, S. &amp; Canzi, M.] The effect of lexical frequency on vowel phonation as a correlate of /t/-glottaling</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/glottaling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/glottaling/</guid>
      <description>Presentations Coretta, S. &amp;amp; Canzi, M. The effect of lexical frequency on vowel phonation as a correlate of /t/-	glottaling. Talk presented at the Linguistic Association of Great Britain (LAGB) conference at the University of Sheffield.
Abstract Introduction. Lexical frequency is known to modulate the effects of a phonetic bias on speech production, such that high-frequency words show a stronger effect for a particular bias since they are exposed more often to that bias (Bybee 2004).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Canzi, M.] Inter- and intra- speaker variation of F(0, 1, 2) &amp; vowel duration in soft, neutral and loud speech in Italian.</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/forensic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/forensic/</guid>
      <description>Conferences Canzi, M. (2018) The Forensic implications of comparing soft, neutral and loud speech. Talk presented at the Manchester Forum in Linguistics (mFiL) at	The University of Manchester
Canzi, M (2018) A quantitative analysis of inter- and intra- speaker variation of F0, F1, F2 and vowel duration in soft, neutral and loud speech in Italian. Poster presented at the British Association of Academics in Phonetics (BAAP) at the University of Kent.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
