<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Massimiliano Canzi</title>
    <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Massimiliano Canzi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://mcanzi.github.io/project/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>information flow order in speech perception</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/erp/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/erp/</guid>
      <description>Overview Aims and Objectives
• To explore how different levels of speech processing interact with each other to facilitate the understanding of speech.
• To test experimentally the relative timing of different levels in speech processing.
• To collect EEG (electroencephalography) data from a relevant sample size on brain re- sponses to auditory stimuli.
Background: Two main currents of thought in psycholinguistics have categorised speech per- ception to be either unidirectional or interactive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the effect of lexical frequency on vowel phonation as a correlate of t glottaling.</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/glottaling/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Sep 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/glottaling/</guid>
      <description>Presentations 2018 Stefano Coretta, Massimiliano Canzi The effect of lexical frequency on vowel phonation as a correlate of /t/- glottaling. Talk presented at the Linguistic Association of Great Britain (LAGB) conference in Sheffield, UK. 11-14th September, 2018.
Resources You can find the research compendium (including data, analysis, code and slides/poster) for this project at the following link:
LAGB 2018
Abstract Introduction. Lexical frequency is known to modulate the effects of a phonetic bias on speech production, such that high-frequency words show a stronger effect for a particular bias since they are exposed more often to that bias (Bybee 2004).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>the forensic implications of comparing soft, neutral and loud speech.</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/forensic/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 11 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/project/forensic/</guid>
      <description>Presentations 2018 Massimiliano Canzi The Forensic implications of comparing soft, neutral and loud speech. Talk presented at the Manchester Forum in Linguistics (mFiL) in Manchester, UK. 26-27th April, 2018.
2018 Massimiliano Canzi A quantitative analysis of inter- and intra- speaker variation of F0, F1, F2 and vowel duration in soft, neutral and loud speech in Italian. Poster presented at the Colloquium of the British Association of Academic Phoneticians (BAAP) in Canterbury, UK.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>