<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>ggplot on Massimiliano Canzi</title>
    <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/tags/ggplot/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ggplot on Massimiliano Canzi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://mcanzi.github.io/tags/ggplot/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Twitter data and sentiment scores in R and Python</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/posts/iii/twittr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/posts/iii/twittr/</guid>
      <description>Getting started Turn on dark mode in the right hand corner of this website for the best experience
 Introduction The aim of this brief post is to present an introduction to the collection and analysis of Twitter data with R and Python. Tweets are extracted in R. Sentiment analysis is carried out in Python with nltk and VADER. The sentiment scores, combined with the previously acquired twitter data, aree then brought back into R for a visual exploration using ggplot() and tidyverse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Introduction to data visualisation with R and ggplot</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/posts/ii/ggplot/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/posts/ii/ggplot/</guid>
      <description>Setup &amp;amp; packages Packages The focus of this introductory, code-along workshop is to get you acquainted with the basic syntax of the ggplot() package, as well as to provide sample code that you can later on expand for the analysis of your own data.
The tidyverse packages include ggplot2, the package focus of this workshop, as well as other useful additions. The packages of the tidyverse universe have been created to work seamlessly together, often times replacing basic R functions with more elegant, efficient solutions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>academic skills</title>
      <link>https://mcanzi.github.io/skills/skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://mcanzi.github.io/skills/skills/</guid>
      <description>Speech Analysis:	Praat, Wavesurfer
Speech Manipulation:	Praat, iZotope, Audacity
ERP/EEG:	Matlab, ERPlab/EEGlab, ActiView, Biosemi EEG systems
Experimental Design:	Presentation (Neurobehavioral Systems), PsychoPy, E-Prime
Statistical Analysis &amp;amp; Data Visualisation:	R (w/ tidyverse), Python
Image and video manipulation Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Lightroom, Adobe Premiere Pro
Languages Italian (Native), English (C2), Portuguese (B2), German (A1)
Other programming languages known:	Python
Text typesetting:	TeX, Microsoft Word</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
